Finding Aid for the Carol Burnett Papers PASC.0066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1956-2005; Series 3.; 34 manuscript boxes; 56 flat boxes
  - Carol Burnett Show (The), 1966-1978; Subseries 4.; 9 manuscript boxes; 35 flat boxes
    - Photograph, undated; 1 photograph; 11"x14", color (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Photograph of Carol Burnett in "vamp" costume.
    - Photograph, 1971; Photograph; 11"x14", b/w (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Contains promotional photograph of Rita Hayworth and Carol Burnett dressed as charwoman characters. Hayworth appeared on the Carol Burnett Show in 1971.
    - Photographic negatives, 1967-1978; 3 photographic negatives; 4" X 5", b/w (Box 60, Folder 6)
      Contains images of Carol Burnett, Harvey Korman and unidentified man in costume.
    - Photographs, 1967-1978; 12 photographs; various sizes, b/w (Box 60, Folder 5)
      Contains production stills and portraits from the Carol Burnett Show including: Carol Burnett, Betty Grable, Martha Raye, Lyle Waggoner, Imogene Coca, Jonathon Winters, Durward Kirby, Sid Caesar.
    - Pink (#309) (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Guests: Andy Griffith. Parts: Saxes TACET, Trumpets TACET, Trombones TACET, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar TACET, Percussion, Harp, Piano.
    - Pink (#309) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Plaque of Goodbye Sketch, March 28, 1978; Wooden plaque; 25"x17 1/2" (Box 61)
      Wooden plaque of a layout in Variety featuring the script pages of the Carol Burnett Show's The Goodbye Sketch featuring Tim Conway and Carol Burnett; written by Conway.
    - Press clippings, 1970, 1977; 1 folder; loose press clippings (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Contains press clippings for the Carol Burnett Show.
    - Press clippings, 1967; 1 folder; loose press clippings (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Press clippings from newspapers, industry trade journals and magazines regarding The Carol Burnett Show in 1967. Clippings not arranged in any order.
    - Press clippings, 1967; 1 folder; loose press clippings (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1967; 1 folder; loose press clippings (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1967; 1 folder; loose press clippings (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Press clippings from newspapers, trade journals and magazines regarding The Carol Burnett Show in 1967. Clippings not arranged in any order.
    - Press clippings, 1967; 2 envelopes; loose press clippings (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1967; 2 envelopes; loose press clippings (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1967; 2 envelopes (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1967; 2 envelopes (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Primitive Man (#0105) (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violas, Celli, Harp, Bass, Drums, Guitar.
    - Primitive Man (#0105) (Box 35, Folder 1)
      "Primitive Man," by Cole Porter (pub. Harms); "They don't make 'em like that," by Elmer Bernstein and Carolyn Leigh (pub. Edwin Morris). Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Violins (orig. + 3 copies); Percussion (orig. + 3 copies); Orig. Lead Sheet + 1 copy.
    - Primitive Tag (#0105) (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Primitive Tag (#0105) (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies); Violins (orig. + 3 copies); Percussion (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Production stills, [1968-1974]; 5 photographs; 8" x 10", b/w & color (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Production stills from the Carol Burnett Show. Includes Burnett and Lyle Waggoner.
    - Production stills, [1970-1978]; 7 photographs; 8"x10", b/w (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Production stills from the Carol Burnett Show. Includes: Burnett, Vicki Lawrence, Tim Conway, Harvey Korman, Jim Nabors
    - Production stills, 1975; 2 photographs; 8"x10", b/w (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Productions stills from the Carol Burnett Show with Burnett and Cher.
    - Program, Carol Burnett Show, Sydney Opera House, [early 1970s]; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Program of a the Carol Burnett Show performing at the Sydney Opera House.
    - Rainy Days and Mondays, If I Could Write A Song (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Parts: Vocal Conductor (2 copies), Percussion, 1st Rhythm Guitar, 2nd Electric Guitar, 1st Trombone, Bass, Drums, Oboe, 2nd Trumpet, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trombone, Alto Flute, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Piano (2 copies), Voices (2 copies).
    - Room Full of Roses, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      Conductor score; original folder marked: "Room Full of Rose 2234 Carol Burnett Sketch Key D [flat]."
    - Room Full of Roses (#19; 2263), undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
      [Carol Burnett Show] Conductor (2 copies).Orchestral parts: 1-5 Reed; 1-4 Trumpet; 1-3 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Harp; A-C Violin; Viola; Cello; Bass; 1-2 Drums. Conductor score: Rehearsal Pianist; Production. Original folder marked: "Room Full of Roses 2234 Carol Burnett Sketch Key D flat."
    - Rose Garden, If I Could Write A Song (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), Vocal Conductor (2 copies), Electric Guitar 2, Percussion, Rhythm Guitar 1, Trombone 1, Bass, Drums, Trumpet 2, Trombone 2, Trumpet 1, Baritone sax, Cello, Viola, Violin (4 copies).
    - Rose-Bows (#003) (Box 4, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Carol & Jim Nabors. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums, Piano.
    - Rosie (#003) (Box 4, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol & Jim Nabors. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, Baritone Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion (2 copies), Drums, Piano.
    - Rosie (#003), undated (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
      Guests: Jim Nabors. Artist: Carol & Jim Nabors. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Sad Grab (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Sad Grab (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Saturday Morning, If I Could Write A Song (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), Vocal Conductor.
    - Script, 1976; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Final revision: December 1, 1976; prod. #0014; air seq. #13; tape: December 3, 1976; air date: December 18, 1976; guest: Dick Van Dyke; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1976; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Final revision: December 8, 1976; prod. #0015; air seq. #19; tape date: December 10, 1976; air date: February 5, 1977; guest: Helen Reddy; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1976-1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Final revision: December 15, 1976; prod. #0016; air seq. #16; tape date: December 17, 1976; air date: January 15, 1977; guest: Glen Campbell; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Final revision: January 5, 1977; prod. #0017; air seq. #17; tape date: January 7, 1997; air date: January 22, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Final revision: January 12, 1977; prod. #0018; air seq. #18; tape date; January 14, 1977; air date: January 29, 1977; guests: Steve Lawrence, Rock Hudson; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Final revision: January 19, 1977; prod. #0019; air: #22; tape date: January 21, 1977; air date: March 19, 1977; guest Hal Linden; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Final revision: February 2, 1977; prod. #0020; air: #20; tape date: February 4, 1977; air date: February 12, 1977; guest: Eydie Gorme; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Script; photo copy (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Final revision: February 9, 1997; prod. #0021; air seq. #21; tape date: February 11, 1977; air date: February 26, 1977; guest: Ben Vereen; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Final revision: February 17, 1977; prod. #0022; air seq. #24; tape date: February 18, 1977; air date: March 26, 1977; guest: Ken Berry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Final revision: March 2, 1977; prod. #0023; air seq. #23; tape date: March 4, 1977; air date: March 19, 1977; guest: Neil Sedaka; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 11, Folder 11)
      First draft: March 21, 1977; prod. #0024; air seq. #25; tape date: March 24, 1977; air date: April 2, 1977; family show, 1 1/2 hrs.; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Final revision: August 24, 1977; prod. #0101; air seq. #4; tape date: August 26, 1977; air date: October 15, 1977; guest: Nancy Dussault; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Final revision: August 31, 1977; prod. #0102; air seq. #8; tape date: September 2, 1977; air date: November 11, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Final revision: September 7, 1977; prod. #0103; air seq. #2; tape date: September 9, 1977; air date: October 1, 1977; guest: Steve Lawrence; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Final revision: September 14, 1977; prod. #0104; air seq. #1; tape date: September 16, 1977; air date: September 24, 1977; guest: Jim Nabors; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Final revision: September 28, 1977; prod. #0105; air seq. #5; tape date: September 30, 1977; air date: October 8, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Final revision: October 5, 1977; prod. #0106; air seq. #6; tape date: October 7, 1977; air date: October 29, 1977; guest: Ken Berry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Final revision: October 12, 1977; prod. #0107; air seq. #05; tape date: October 14, 1977; air date: October 22, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Final revision: October 19, 1977; prod. #0108; air seq. #7; tape date: October 21, 1977; air date: November 5, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Final revision: November 2, 1977; prod. #0109; air seq. #9; tape date: November 4, 1977; air date: November 19, 1977; guest: Ben Vereen; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Final revision: November 9, 1977; prod. #0110; air seq. #10; tape date: November 11, 1977; air date: November 26, 1977; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Final revision: November 16, 1977; prod. #0111; air seq. #11; tape date: November 18, 1977; air date: December 3, 1977; guest: Bernadette Peters; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Final revision: November 30, 1977; prod. #0112; air seq. #12; tape date: December 2, 1977; air date; December 11, 1977; guest: Rock Hudson; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Final revision: December 7, 1977; prod. #0113; air seq. #13; tape date: December 9, 1977; air date: December 18, 1977; guests: Helen Redd and Ken Berry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1977; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Final revision: December, 14, 1977; prod. #0114; air seq. #15; tape date: December 16, 1977; air date: January 1, 1978; guest: Steve Lawrence; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Final revision: January 4, 1978; prod. #0015; air seq. #16; tape date: January 6, 1978; air date: January 8, 1978; guest: Roddy McDowall and Ken Berry; annotations and rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Final revision: January 18, 1978; prod. #0117; air seq. #18; tape date: January 20, 1978; air date: January 29, 1978; guest: Steve Lawrence, The Captain and Tennille; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Final draft: January 25, 1978; prod. #0118; air seq. #19; tape date: January 27, 1978; air date: February 5, 1978; guests: Natalie Cole, Ken Berry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Final revision: February 1, 1978; prod. #0119; air seq. #20; tape date: February 3, 1978; air date: February 19, 1978; guest: Ken Berry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Final revision: February 15, 1978; prod. #0120; air seq. #21; tape date: February 17, 1978; air date: February 26, 1978; guest: Steve Lawrence; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Final revision: February 22, 1978; prod. #0121; air seq. #22; tape date: February 24, 1978; air date: March 5, 1978; guests: Steve Martin, Betty White; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Final revision: March 1, 1978; prod. #0122; air seq. #23; tape date: March 3, 1978; air date: March 12, 1978; guests: James Garner, George Carlin, Ken Barry; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Final revision: March 8, 1978; prod. #0123; air seq. #24; tape date: March 10, 1978; air date: March 19, 1978; guests: Steve Lawrence, Bernadette Peters; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1978; Photocopy (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Final revision: March 15, 1978; prod. #0124; air seq. #25; tape date: March 17, 1978; air date: March 29, 1978; 2 hour special; family show; annotations and show rundown included.
    - Script, 1967; 1 script; 72 pages with revisions (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Show no. #4; prod. # 006; tape date: September 23, 1967; [air date] October 2, 1967; annotations included.
    - Signals (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Parts: Lead Sheet/Guitar Score
    - Signals (Club Arrangement), Nightclub Act #1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Parts: Reed 1 (+ orig.), Reed 2 (+ orig.), Reed 3 (+ orig.), Reed 4 (+ orig.), Reed 5 (+ orig.), Trumpet 1 (+ orig.), Trumpet 2 (+ orig.), Trumpet 3 (+ orig.), Trumpet 4 (+ orig.; Addition Trumpet 4 also H. Zimmerman's included), Trombone 1 (+ orig.; Addition Trombone 1 also H. Zimmerman's included), Trombone 2 (+ orig.; Addition Trombone 2 also H. Zimmerman's included) (Note: Trombone 1 and Trombone 2 have an additional rewrite.), Trombone 3 (+ orig.; Addition Trumpet 4 also Orville Knapp's included), Violin A (orig. + 2 copies), Violin B (orig. + 2 copies), Viola (+ orig.), Cello (orig. + 2 copies), Bass (+ orig.), Guitar (Zimmerman's part + orig.), Guitar (Williams part), Percussion 1 (orig. + 3 copies), Oboe (+ orig.), Bassoon (+ orig.), Flute (+ orig.), Percussion 2 (+ orig.), Harp (orig.).
    - Signals (Club Arrangement) (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Nightclub Act #1. Master Score 1, Master Score 2, Master Score 3; Piano, Conductor Score (Original + 2 copies).
    - Sing You Singers, udated (Box 57, Folder 14)
      Conductor score (3 copies [2 Piano].)
    - Sing You Sinners, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Conductor score: Piano (3 copies). Orchestral parts: 1-4 Reed; 1-2 Trumpet; 1 Trombone; 1-2 Percussion; Guitar; Bass; 1-2 Drums.
    - Small Slush (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Small Slush (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 14)
      "The Slush" (Outside In The Snow): Stan Freeman, ASCAP Punkin Publishing. Master Score; Conductor Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Snow Grab (#0106) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Snow Grab (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Someone to Watch Over Me, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Sondheim Finale - "Salute To Stephen Sondheim" (#0107) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violins (orig. +3 copies), Violas, Celli, Harp, Bass, Drums, Percussion (orig. + 3 copies), Guitar, Lead Sheet (8 copies + 1 partial). See also boxes 23, 24.
    - Sondheim Finale - "Salute To Stephen Sondheim" (#0107) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Parts. See also boxes 22, 24.
    - Sondheim Finale - "Salute To Stephen Sondheim" (#0107) (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Parts. See also boxes 22, 23.
    - Sondheim Finale - "Salute To Stephen Sondheim" (#0107) (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Master Score; Conductor Score (orig. + 3 copies).
    - Stamp, Stamp, Stamp (#0422) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Artist: Harvey Korman. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums, Harp, Piano, Lead Sheet.
    - Stamp, Stamp, Stamp (#0422) (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Artist: Harvey Korman. Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - Summer of '76 Overture (Carol Burnett-Vegas), Nightclub Act No. 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Reed 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Violins (orig. + 4 copies), Violas (orig + 1 copy), Celli (orig + 1 copy), Percussion (orig + 2 copies), Guitar, Bass, Drums.
    - Summer of '76 Overture (Carol Burnett-Vegas), Nightclub Act No. 1 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Conductor Score (orig. + 2 copies); Master Score.
    - Sunrise Sunset, If I Could Write A Song (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), Flugel Horn 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 1, Trumpet 2, Rhythm Guitar, Flute, Electric Guitar, Bass, Drums, 1st Percussion, Violin (4 copies), Cello, Viola, Piano, Harp, 2nd Percussion.
    - Sunrise Sunset, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Master Score; Conductor Score (2 copies).
    - Sweet Georgia Brown, udated (Box 57, Folder 6)
      Conductor score. Originally in binder with other songs I Can't Say No and Mongolier-Intro marked "605."
    - Tea For Two (#0405) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Parts: Percussion (orig.), Violin (orig.), 1 Flute, 2 Flute, 3 Flute, 4 Clarinet, 5 Clarinet, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Guitar, Bass, Percussion (3 copies), Drums, Piano, Harp.
    - Tea For Two (#0405) (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Guests: Pat Carroll, Art Carney. Master Score.
    - Tell it Like It Is, Magda (#028) (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Choir Score (5 copies), Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Tell it Like It Is, Magda (#028), undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Master Score. Conductor Score. Lead Sheet.
    - Tenth Anniversary Guest Book, 1976-1977; Hard back book (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Contains autographs and salutations from show guests inlcuding Rock Hudson, Madeline Kahn, Roddy McDowell and others.
    - The Christmas Song, If I Could Write A Song (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Parts: Violin (4 copies), Bass/Piano (2 copies), 2nd Electric Guitar, Oboe, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trombone, Drums, 1st Trombone, Cello, Viola, Vocal Conductor, Voices (2 copies), Percussion (2 copies), 1st Rhythm Guitar, 2nd Trumpet.
    - The Christmas Song, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - The Varsity Drag (#0422) (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violin (3 copies), Viola, Cello, Percussion (2 copies), Bass, Guitar, Drums, Harp, Piano, Lead Sheet.
    - The Varsity Drag (#0422) (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Master Score; Conductor Score.
    - This Mystery (#0422) (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Artists: Carol Burnett, Harvey Korman. Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax 5, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trumpet 4, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violins A, Violins B, Violins C, Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Percussion, Drums, Harp, Piano, Lead Sheet.
    - This Mystery (#0422) (Box 21, Folder 3)
      Artists: Carol Burnett, Harvey Korman. Master Score; Production Score (2 copies).
    - Those Were The Days, If I Could Write A Song (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), Trumpet 2, Trombone 2, Trombone 1, Trumpet 1, Rhythm Guitar 2, Tenor Sax, Rhythm Guitar 1, Bass, Drums, 1st Percussion, Violin (4 copies), Cello, Viola, Piano, Harp, 2nd Percussion.
    - Those Were The Days, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Trixie (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Conductor Score. Parts: Guitar, Drums, Bass.
    - Try To Remember, If I Could Write A Song (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Parts: Voices (2 copies), 2nd Trumpet, 2nd Trombone, 1st Trombone, 1st Trumpet, Rhythm Guitar, Flute, Electric Guitar, Bass, Drums, 2nd Percussion, Violin (4 copies), Cello, Viola, Piano, Harp, 1st Percussion (2 copies).
    - Try To Remember, If I Could Write A Song (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Up Above My Head (#028) (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Parts: Alto Sax 1, Alto Sax 2, Tenor Sax 3, Tenor Sax 4, Baritone Sax, Violin (orig. + 3 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass (Fender), Guitar, Percussion (orig. + 1 copy), Drums, Harp, Piano.
    - Up Above My Head (#028), undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Master Score. Conductor Score (2 copies). Choir Score. Lead Sheet (2 copies).
    - Watch What Happens (#007) (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Guests: Imogene Coca & Lainie Kazan. Artist: Carol & Lainie Kazan. Parts: 1st Alto Sax, 2nd Alto Sax, 3rd Tenor Sax, 4th Tenor Sax, 1st Trumpet, 2nd Trumpet, 3rd Trumpet, 4th Trumpet, 1st Trombone, 2nd Trombone, 3rd Trombone, 4th Trombone, Violin (4 copies), Viola, Cello, Bass, Guitar, Drums, Percussion, Harp, Piano
    - Watch What Happens (#007), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Guests: Imogene Coca & Lainie Kazan. Artist: Carol & Lainie Kazan. Master Score; Conductor Score (6 copies); Production Score (2 copies).
    - Weather Girl (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Piano/Conductor Score.
    - Weather Girl (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Piano/Conductor Score (orig.).
    - Well/Nowhere (#802) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Artist: Michelle Lee and Cast. Parts: Reed 1, Reed 2, Reed 3, Reed 4, Trumpet 1, Trumpet 2, Trumpet 3, Trombone 1, Trombone 2, Trombone 3, Trombone 4, Violins (orig. +3 copies), Violas, Celli, Harp, Bass, Percussion (orig. + 2 copies), Choir Score (2 copies), Guitar, Drums.
    - Well/Nowhere (#802) (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Guests: Michelle Lee, Jack Weston. Artist: Michelle Lee and Cast. Master Score; Conductor Score (Original + 3 copies); Lead Sheet (orig.).
    - Whiffenpoof Song (Miss Alto) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Piano/Conductor Score (orig.). Also: Percussion part for "Mama A Rainbow."
    - Woe (#0106) (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Woe (#0106) (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Yesterday I Heard The Rain (#0311) (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Master score.
    - Zing Dinga Linga (#0422) (Box 19, Folder 3)